[Music]
[Música]
Yes, Dallas has commented on Chocas just
si dallas ha opinado sobre el chocas
now, 5 minutes ago, 5 or 10 minutes ago, he
hace nada hace 5 minutos 5 o 10 minutos
posted exactly, I never liked
ha puesto exactamente nunca me cayó bien
Chocas, he
el chocas
says, in fact, he criticized you and said
dice de hecho te hizo una crítica y dijo
that you were the typical boy who cries, I mean, to be
que eras el típico chico que llora
fair, well,
o sea siendo justo con la verdad
he doesn't cry or anything, well, we've
pues anda que no llora él ni nada bueno
already seen the best, being
pues ya hemos visto lo mejor siendo
fair, what happens is that I'm not going to
justo lo que pasa que ya eso no lo voy a
find that, no way, I did
encontrar ni de coña
n't see it against him, no way, I have
no lo vio en contra ni de coña tengo
a reaction here
aquí una reacción
and a reaction from
y una reacción de
[Music]
[Música]
from Chocas, it's been eight months,
del chocas mí ya tiene ocho meses ya
okay, here you can see it and they sound in
vale aquí lo podéis ver y me suenan a
favor to me, it's really
favor ya de memoria de verdad
impossible to remember what he
imposible acordarme de memoria de lo que
said, but I would swear that he defended Dallas, I would swear that he has
dijo pero juraría que defendió a dallas
defended Dallas for 8
juraría que ha defendido a dallas 8
months, Chosa gets involved with the Ceiba issue,
meses choca se moja con el tema de la
but this is something else, a little
pero esto es otra cosa
hectic, it's known that in the morning and I have like
movidito sabido que a la mañana y tengo
100 mentions, then you criticize on the
unas 100 menciones luego criticais en
internet and all that because you're a bunch of
internet y tal porque sois una panda de
jerks, I mean, what happens is that,
[__] o sea lo que pasa es que
well, look at them  I could be already already into
pues míralos a ellos yo podría ser ya ya
the subject it is not mobile and thing
metido en el tema no es móvil y cosa
could be that this channel
podría ser que este canal
that only uploads this
que sólo sube esto
is the choca also dude that would be
sea el choca también tío ya sería la
great no
[__] no
this was a
este fue un canal
given channel welcome hey thank you very much to
dado bienvenido oye muchas gracias a
all of you who have
todos los que os habéis hecho miembros
become members hey thank you very much it is greatly appreciated we are really going through a bit of a rough time with youtube and with the multiple accounts that you left on youtube in one comment it says that he is a fan of yours he surely watches you always no no no and in a
te ve siempre no no no y en un
comment it is in a
comentario lo pone en un comentario de
youtube comment we have seen it but because this
youtube lo hemos visto pero porque este
channel
canal
was the channel that uploaded this video the
fue el canal que subió este vídeo el
choca explodes and responds to the
choque se explota y responde a la
ability it
habilidad
could be that he is out he choca
yo podría ser que esté fuera él choca
too
también
and that it was the only channel that uploaded done
y que fue el único canal que subió hecho
dude
tío
and if you notice he only uploads click on the choca you
y si os fijáis sólo sube click del choca
could jazz sometimes that you no longer think
podrías jazz a veces que ya no se piensa
about anything it
en nada
is not crazy nothing
no es loco nada
that he did not want to answer me
que él no me haya querido responder
directly
directamente
then he mentioned me in that live without
entonces me mencionó en ese directo sin
mentioning my name he mentions me
mencionar mi nombre me menciona a mí
and he took it and uploaded it to a range channel
y lo coja y lo suba a un canal rango
so that people know that that answer
para que la gente sepa que esa respuesta
is for me you understand
va para mí me entendéis
but well getting back to the subject a little
pero bueno volviendo un poco al tema
let's go  to look for some rhinestones whatever we
vamos a buscar algún strass tillo
say
lo que digamos
time
el tiempo
dad
papá
but putting yourself in the situation of having
pero ponerse en la situación de haber
suffered something like what you suffered, it
sufrido algo como lo que sufrió haber
is a
que es una
false accusation of gender violence
denuncia falsa de violencia de género
that people take it as a joke
que la gente se lo toma muy a broma tal
but living it must be
pero que vivirlo tiene que ser
complicated it must be very complicated
complicado tiene que ser muy complicado
because the judge from what I read out there on the
porque el juez por lo que leí por ahí en
internet
internet
the judge really ruled that it was
el juez realmente dictaminó que era
false it was a false accusation
falso era una denuncia falsa
well that there is no such thing
bueno eso eso no lo hay
more than anything he defended the city in the video
más que nada defendía en el vídeo de la
more than anything he defended it in
ciudad a las más que nada lo defendía en
the video but well
el vídeo pero bueno
the attitude of Choca has
la actitud del choca siempre ha echado
always put me back down I've always said it I've been saying it for a long time his followers canceled me but well to Dallas for being Dallas well they're not going to take my opinion into account okay
van a tener la opinión en cuenta vale
but it's been brutal man today has
pero ha sido brutal tío el día de hoy ha
been brutal and Ximo has put something else the
sido brutal y ximo ha puesto algo más el
hotel Dallas we
hotel dallas
give it to him he
le damos
knows pop well nothing well he
le sabe el pop bueno pues nada pues el
has said little
solo poco ha dicho
surely Dallas well if he could he would say
seguramente dallas pues si pudiera diría
something like me if you knew how many people
algo como yo si supierais la de gente
come to visit and then throw [ __ ] at us
que va de visita y luego nos tira [__]
and then don't throw [ __ ] they see you better with a
y luego no tira [__] te ven mejor con
beard the truth is more youthful with  my beard looks
barba la verdad más juventud con barba
younger on the contrary it does
se me ve con más juventud al contrario
n't look younger now let's see it
no se ve ahora más joven a ver me la
takes my hand because I couldn't find the comb
quita la mano porque no encontraba el
brush of the fight no the
peine del cepillo de la pendencia no el
comb of Miguel' of Jacques and Javi I couldn't
peine de miguel' de jacques y javi no
find the comb for today here I can't
encontraba el peine para hoy aquí no
see from here coming what now on
puedo ver de aquí venir lo que ahora en
twitter I think I couldn't find the comb
twitter creo que no encontraba el peine
for shaving measurements and to have shaved
para medidas de afeitarme y haberme
in another way you know to have
rasurado de otra forma sabe haberme
left me I like then I was
dejado a mí me gusta entonces iba
running I was in a hurry to go live
corriendo tenía prisa para directo
because I showered 15 minutes before
porque me he duchado 15 minutos antes de
the live
del directo
people are freaking out I
la gente está flipando
admit it I'm from the say something else well you
lo admito soy de la dice algo más
are a very handsome Dallas
pues eres un dallas muy guapo
Ryan
ryan
freaking out with this
flipando con esto
the moment we can has been very strong
el momento podemos ha sido muy fuerte
uncle
tío
khatibi
khatibi
the truth the evening of the year the khatibi clash
la verdad la velada del año el choque
or something when people leave
o algo cuando la gente se patio
when people know the
cuando la gente sepa el
roll man a roll that happened to my
rollo tío un rollo que me ha pasado a mi
uncle
tío
the role of collides with Katie has been good we
el rol de choca con katie ha sido bueno
have to say it
hay que decirlo
when people know and when I can
cuando la gente sepa y cuando yo pueda
tell a mom roll that happens to me
contar un rollo de mamá que me pasa a mí
and that I leave without money obviously
y que me vaya sin dinero evidentemente
wind waker thank you very much probably not  They
wind waker muchas gracias seguramente no
have to tell it, with that I say it
lo tengan que contar yo con eso lo digo
all, yes, Pep, to Cameo, daughter, Cameo, we've already
todo si pep a cameo hija cameo ya te
seen you around here with the cameos,
hemos visto por aquí con los cameos
and also because there are many people who are here,
y además porque hay mucha gente que está
when I tell that, I probably won't
cuando yo cuente eso seguramente no me
even need to tell it because it will
va a hacer falta ni contarlo porque van
be them that you downloaded, I
a ser ellos que descargaste
just read a drawing of a fig over
acabo de leer un dibujo de una breva por
there, a drawing, a fig, no way, old lady,
ahí un dibujo una breve no vale no
be the best, I'm playing a lot,
vieja ser el mejor estoy jugando mucho
the job position here, a drawing,
el puesto aquí de trabajo un dibujo no
nothing's happening, a
pasa nada
drawing from the past, a drawing from the past,
un dibujo pasado
name Mons, a drawing
nombre mons
sounded, a drawing, something's happening, it's a
sonó un dibujo un dibujo pasa algo sea
drawing from today,
un dibujo de hoy
the drawing, something's happening,
el dibujo pasa algo
a drawing of a grapefruit, I think so,
un dibujo de un pomelo
seriously,
en serio
a drawing,
un dibujo
they are messengers, option, I do
son mensajeras opción
n't think so, let's
no creo
go, I'm not playing it, I'll delete it just in
vamos no me la juego lo borro por si
case, okay, family, well, I'm going,
acaso ya bueno familia pues me voy nos
see you, see you, see you
vemos nos vemos nos vemos
[Music]
[Música]